bmyers.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

We are strongly committed to safeguarding visitor and subscriber privacy on bmyers.com. We operate under the following strict privacy policy: 

The only information we obtain about our visitors or subscribers is information we need to process credit card charges for subscription fees. The information collected is never revealed, sold, or made public for any reason.

Personally identifiable information provided by subscribers (name, email or home address, etc.) is never disclosed to any individual or business. 

**Cookies**  
Each time a subscriber logs into bmyers.com, we store a temporary 'cookie' in the browser files of that subscriber's computer. This cookie is used during your online session to allow you free access to the Subscribers Area, without repeatedly requiring you to re-enter your user name and password.

When you log off or leave the site, the cookies file is automatically removed.

 **External Links**  
In order to provide visitors with greater value, some of our pages may provide links to various third party websites. In no case is subscriber information or 'cookies' provided to the third party sites.

However, keep in mind that many sites do attempt to capture visitor information when you browse those sites. Once you leave our site, we are not able to alert you should another site attempt to gather information from your browser.

 **Private Forums**  
We provide our subscribers with a multi-tiered Discussion Forum that makes sharing information with other subscribers easy. To protect your privacy when posting or replying to messages in the message board, your personal information and email is not revealed.

However, remember that any information you disclose in the message board areas can be read by all other subscribers, so exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**  
We use a variety of security measures including encryption and authentication from Thawte to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under our control. 

**Choice/Opt-In**  
Our site gives users the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. You can be assured that we never reveal, sell, or make available your email address to anyone for any purpose. This site also gives users options for removing their information from our database in order to stop receiving our communications. 

**Other**  
If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, feel free to contact us.
